minionclix.com 2016-06-08

# EasyCloud - Easy PHP Cloud Hosting » Pages » Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy was last revised on October 20, 2011.

EasyCloud ("we" or "us") is concerned about privacy and security of our customers. We know that you care how your personal information is used and shared. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of personal data we collect.

This document explains what information of yours will be collected by EasyCloud when you use the EasyCloud services, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of information.

We won't spam you or sell your personal information to others.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We will only collect, use, and share your information as we describe in this Privacy Policy or as you give us a permission to do.

#### What Do We Collect

###### Information Provided by a Customer

You provide us information about yourself, such as your name and e-mail address, when you register for an account with EasyCloud. You also provide us information in the content you post to be hosted at our service. If you correspond with us by email, we may retain the content of your email messages, your email address and our responses.

###### Cookies

We may place a cookie on your hard drive during the web visit. A cookie is a unique alphanumeric identifier that we use to help us identify the number of unique visitors to our Website, whether or not those visitors are repeat visitors, and the source of the visits. Cookies cannot be executed as code or used to deliver a virus. Other servers cannot read them and personal information cannot be gathered from them. They are simply an identifier shared between you and us to allow us to improve the services we offer to you through our Website. If you do not wish cookies to be placed on your computer, then they can be disabled in your web browser. The option to do so is normally found in your browser's "security settings" section. However, please note, permanently disabling cookies in your browser may hinder your use of our Website as well as other websites and interactive services.

###### Log Files

When you use our website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, referring or exit pages and their URLs, number of clicks, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information.

###### Web Beacons

A web beacon, also known as clear gif image, is a small graphic (usually 1 pixel x 1 pixel), that may be embedded in a web advertisement, email, or page on our web site, but is invisible to you. When you view a page on our web site, an email or an advertisement your web browser may request the web beacon from a web server, which in turn will set a cookie in your web browser containing a unique identifier. This unique identifier will be linked to log information that is used to track your movements on our web site in order to determine the effectiveness of content and advertising campaigns. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make EasyCloud better for our users. No personally identifiable information from your EasyCloud account is collected using thee web beacons. 

#### How We Use The Collected Information

###### Personal Information

We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of our service. We may use your information to process your service requests, handle orders, deliver products and services, process payments, communicate with you about orders, provide access to secure areas of the Website, recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you, to personalize your visit to our Website, and to enable us to review develop and continually improve the products services and offers we provide on-line. We also use this information to prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our Website and to enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

###### Web Visit Information

We use the **visitors' IP address** to diagnose and/or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with certain IP addresses. We use **log files** to analyze websites' statistic information and identify issues with our servers and our customers' websites. We use **cookies** to help us recognize visitors as unique visitors when they return to our websites. We use **web beacons** to count the number of times that our advertisements and web-based email content are viewed. We combine web beacon information with cookies to track activity on our website originating from advertisements and web-based email content.

#### Security of Collected Information

EasyCloud is committed to industry's best practices approaches concerning security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information in our possession. We use various security measures to protect the information we collect, as appropriate to the type of information, including encryption, firewalls, and access controls.

#### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy may also change from time to time. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes, however, we will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personal information collected in the past without your prior consent. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
